Apparently, Index has committed 103,000 grimoires to memory.
（上条(かみじょう)）
インデックスは 頭ん中に―
10万3,000冊の魔道書を
記憶しているらしい
I managed to defeat the magician,
俺は なんとか魔術師を退けたが
インデックスのケガは ひどい
but Index's wounds are severe.
魔術を使えば
治療はできるらしいんだけど
It seems her wounds can be treated with magic,
but the students in this city are all unable to use magic.
この町の学生には
魔術なんてもんは使えない
そんなわけで
ひとつ 小萌(こもえ)先生 頼んます！
So, basically, Komoe-sensei, I'm counting on you.
～♪
#03 Necessarius
The Church of Necessary Evil
（インデックス）
現時刻は…
What is the current local time... in Japan Standard Time?
（インデックス）
日本標準時間で
何時ですか？
それと 日付もお願いします
And the date, please.
７月20日の午後８時半ですけど…
July 20th, 8:30 pm.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
時計を見ていないようですが
その時刻は正確なのですか？
I notice you did not consult a clock.
Is that time accurate?
I don't have a clock in this room.
そもそも
私の部屋には 時計はないですよ
先生の体内時計は 秒刻みで
正確なので 問題ないのです
Sensei's internal clock goes by the second, so that should be accurate.
一定の食生活と運動のリズムで
体内時計くらい調節できるんですよ
I can adjust my internal body clock with a stable diet and exercise pattern.
From the position of the stars and the angle of the moon...
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
星の位置と 月の角度から見て―
シリウス方向に
誤差 0,038で一致しました
...it matches the direction of Sirius with an error of 0.038...
それでは確認します　現時刻は―
Then, to confirm.
The current local time in Japan Standard Time
is July 20th, 8:30 pm, correct?
日本標準時間で ７月20日
午後８時30分でよろしいですね？
Yes, we're at the 53 second mark, to be exact.
はい　正確には
53秒に入ったところですけど
あっ！
…て ダメです 起き上がっちゃ
N-No, you shouldn't get up!
かまいません　再生可能です
Do not worry, regeneration is possible.
The end of Cancer, the period is midnight between 8 to 12.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
かに座の終わり
８時から12時の夜半　方位は西方
Bearing is to the West.
ウインディーネの守護
天使の役はヘルワイム
The guardian of Undine.
The angel is Helheim.
何ですか？　それ
What's... that?
魔術
（小萌）えっ？
Magic.
I will need to borrow your hand and body from this part on.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
ここから先は あなたの手を借りて
あなたの体を借ります
指示のとおりにしてくだされば―
If you follow my instructions,
誰も不幸にならなくて済み
誰にも恨まれずに済みます
no misfortune shall befall anyone here,
and you shall have no need
to bear a grudge against anyone.
いいから 横になって
救急車を待つんです
Just lie down and wait for the ambulance!
Umm... bandage... bandage...
（小萌）
えっと 包帯 包帯っと…
その程度の処置では 私の傷を
完全に塞ぐことは不可能です
Treatment of that level will not suffice in tending to my wounds.
I do not understand the meaning of "ambulance",
“救急車”の意味は
分かりかねますが
それは
あと数分の間に 完全に傷を塞ぎ
but will that be able to completely tend to my wounds in the next few minutes...
...and replenish a sufficient amount of vital energy, mana, to my body?
なおかつ 体内の生命力“マナ”を
必要量 補充することが可能ですか
（小萌）
…で 何をすれば？
先生 魔法少女ではないですよ
Then, what should I do?
Sensei isn't a magical girl, you know?
ご協力に感謝します
I am grateful for your cooperation.
First...
まずは…
...what is that black object over there?
何ですか？　そちらの黒い物は
（小萌）ああ…
This is a memory card for video games.
これは
ゲームのメモリーカードです
それを
テーブルの真ん中に置いてください
Please put that in the middle of the table.
（小萌）
ちゃぶ台ですけどね
It's a mini-dining table, by the way.
Is this a miniature model of this room?
（小萌）
これ…
この部屋のミニチュアなのですか？
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
素材は関係ありません
The materials do not matter.
形と役割が同じなら
儀式は可能です
If the shapes and roles fit,
then the ritual can be carried out.
This is?
（小萌）これは？
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）缶ビールの位置です
The location of your beer cans.
In any case, I would be rather grateful if you followed my instructions accurately.
それより こちらの指示を
正確に行っていただけると幸いです
If you commit a mistake in the process,
手順を踏み間違えた場合
あなたの神経回線と脳内回路を
焼き切るおそれがありますので
there is a possibility your nervous system will be burnt out.
Failure entails the destruction and death of your body... is what I'm telling you...
失敗は あなたの肉体の破壊と
死亡を意味している…
…と告げています
（小萌）えっ？
I will descend the angel and create a temple.
天使を降ろして 神殿を作ります
私のあとに続き 唱えてください
Repeat after me.
ウワッ！
（ぶつける音）
Link successful.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
リンクしました
リンク？
Link?
The temple created atop this table has been successfully linked to this room.
テーブルの上に作った神殿は
この部屋とリンクしています
この部屋で起きたことは
テーブルの上でも起きます
What happens in this room will also occur on the table.
What happens on the table will also occur in this room.
テーブルの上で起きたことは
部屋の中でも起きます
Please image it!
思い浮かべなさい
（小萌）は… はい
W-What?
A golden angel.
金色(こんじき)の天使　体格は子供
２枚の羽を持つ美しい天使の姿
Its physique is that of a child's.
It possesses two wings.
Image the sight of this beautiful angel.
Angel...
天使…
ハァ…
Telling me to think of an angel out of the blue is...
急に天使なんて言われても…
うん？　あ… あれ？
We are not actually summoning an angel.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
本当に天使を
呼んでいるわけではありません
As the mage, you must use your will to create the form of an angel.
術者である あなたの意思で
天使の形を作り込んでいくのです
は… はい
O-Okay!
かわいい天使　かわいい天使
A cute angel...
かわいい天使
かわいい天使　かわいい天使…
A cute angel...
あれ？　ホントに天使を
呼んでるわけじゃない …です？
Huh? I didn't really summon an angel... did I?
ウワッ！
Fixation of the form has failed.
形の固定化に失敗
最低限
ブルーカラーのウインディーネで
At the very least, a blue-colored Undine to protect the temple shall suffice.
神殿を守護できればかまいません
続けます
（小萌）うん
Let's proceed.
A cute angel...
かわいい天使　かわいい天使
かわいい天使…
Along with the replenishment of mana,
マナの補充に伴い
生命の危機の回避を確認
I have confirmed the avoidance of life endangerment.
ヨハネのペンを休眠します
John's Pen will now enter sleep mode.
ハァ…
Are you okay?
大丈夫です？
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
治すには 自分の体力が要るだけ
All that's needed to heal me is my own stamina.
ケガそのものは塞がってるから平気
The wound itself has been treated, so I will be fine.
良かった　背負わせることがなくて
Thank God that he doesn't need to shoulder this.
“背負わせること”？
Shoulder?
If I had died here,
ここで私が死んだら あの人に
背負わせちゃうかもしれないからね
he might have needed to shoulder this.
あなた… 自分のことよりも
上条ちゃんのことを？
You were worried about Kamijyo-chan more than yourself?
I don't know.
分からない
なんだか よく分からないけど
I'm really not sure...
でも…
...but...
And why is it...
（上条）
ていうか―
...that the big beer drinker and smoker, the mature Komoe-sensei's, pajamas...
なんだってビール好きで愛煙家の
大人な小萌先生のパジャマが―
お前にピッタリ合っちまうんだ？
...fit you perfectly?
It's like, how many years apart are you two?
…たく 年齢差 いくつなんだか
Don't snub me like that.
見くびらないでほしい
（小萌）うんうん
PLACEHOLDER
*nod* *nod*
I do feel that my chest feels restricted in these pajamas.
私 もう さすがに このパジャマは
ちょっと胸が苦しいかも
*nod* *nod*
（小萌）
なっ！
そ… その発言はナメてるのです！
Y-Your comment is insulting!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
え～っ？　でも…
But...
（小萌）“でも”何なんですか？
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）別に
But what?
Nothing~
（小萌）
私 大人なんです！
I am an adult!
Anyway, Kamijyo-chan!
ところで 上条ちゃん
結局 この子は
上条ちゃんの何さまなんです？
Ultimately, who is this girl to you?!
う～ん… 妹
My sister...
大ウソにも程があるです！
モロ銀髪 碧眼(へきがん)の外国人少女です！
There are times when you shouldn't be lying!
Sorry! Sorry! I really mean it!
She's a beautiful foreign girl with silver hair and blue eyes!
I lied! Sorry! Sorry!
上条ちゃん
（上条）うん？
Kamijyo-chan!
先生
ひとつだけ聞いてもいいですか？
Sensei, can I ask something?
Desu?
…です
（上条）
事情を聞きたいのは―
Are you asking this to tell
the executive board of Academy City?
このことを 学園都市の
理事会なんかに伝えるためですか？
Desu!
…です
I don't know what kind of trouble you two are in,
上条ちゃんたちが 一体
どんな問題に巻き込まれてるか
分からないですけど
but whatever it is, since it took place inside the city,
それが学園都市の中で起きた以上
解決するのは教師の役目
it is a teacher's job to take care of the problem.
大人の義務です
（上条）う～ん…
It is an adult's duty.
上条ちゃんたちが
危ない橋を渡っていると知って
If I know that you two are treading on dangerous ground,
黙っているほど
先生は子供ではないのです
I am not stupid enough to just stand by and do nothing.
先生が赤の他人だったら
遠慮なく巻き込んでるけど
If you were a complete stranger,
I wouldn't hesitate at all in involving you.
But I owe you a favor, Sensei,
先生には借りがあるんで
巻き込みたくないんです
so I don't want to get you involved.
何気に格好いいセリフを吐いて
ごまかそうったって
Saying something cool like that and trying to cover things up will not make Sensei forgive you.
先生は許さないですよ
（上条）
あれ？　どこへ？
Hey, where're you going?
This is a suspension of negotiations.
執行猶予です
先生 スーパー行って
ご飯のお買い物してくるです
Sensei will now go to the supermarket to buy materials to make breakfast.
In the meantime, Kamijyo-chan, you think about how and what you should tell me, okay?
上条ちゃんは それまでに
何をどう話すべきか―
きっちり かっちり
整理しておくですよ
それと…
（上条）うん？　それと？
And...
And?
先生 お買い物に夢中になってると
忘れるかもしれません
When Sensei gets into shopping too much, she might forget about everything.
帰ってきたら ズルしないで―
When she gets back, Kamijyo-chan, you shouldn't try to play tricks and should just tell her first thing, okay?
上条ちゃんから話してくれなくちゃ
ダメなんですからね
ハァ…
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）ステキな人だね
She's a wonderful person.
うん？　小萌先生のことか？
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）うん
You mean, Komoe-sensei?
Yeah.
これ以上 先生は巻き込めないな
I can't get Sensei any deeper into this.
そう
Yes, we cannot let her use any more magic.
もう あの人は魔術を使っちゃダメ
（上条）うん？
Grimoires are dangerous things,
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
魔道書っていうのは危ないんだよ
そこに書かれている
異なる常識や違(たが)える法則
with the contrasting common wisdom and the altered laws written in them.
そういう違う世界って 善悪の前に
この世界にとっては有毒なの
A "different world" like that is poisonous for "this world", regardless of good and evil.
有毒？
Poisonous?
うん　魔術師なら ともかく―
Without mentioning magicians,
この世界の人間が
違う世界の知識を知ると―
if people of "this world" come in touch with knowledge of a "different world",
それだけで
脳は破壊されてしまうから
their brains will be destroyed just because of that.
破壊って…
魔術って そういうものなのか？
Destroyed?
Is that what magic is like?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
知りたい？
Do you want to know?
私の抱えてるもの
ホントに知りたい？
Do you really want to know the burden I am carrying?
What should I say?
何ていうか それじゃ
こっちが神父さんみてえだな
It's like I'm the Father now.
ホント　懺悔(ざんげ)を聞く神父さんみたい
Yes, you truly are like a Father listening to a confession.
The Christians were originally all united as one,
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
十字教なんて 元はひとつなのに
but why do you think they have split up
into so many different churches?
どうして こんなに
分かれちゃったんだと思う？
（上条）
う～ん… そりゃ…
That's because...
宗教に政治を混ぜたからだよ
Because they brought politics into religion.
分裂し 対立し
バラバラの道を歩くことになった
They split, opposed each other,
and chose various paths of their own...
同じ神さまを信じてるのに
...even though they all believed in the same God...
それぞれが独自の進化を遂げて
個性を手に入れたんだよ
All of them have evolved in their own way and gained their own "personality".
Personality, eh?
個性ね
The English Purist Church that I belong to...
私の所属するイギリス清教は…
イギリスは魔術の国だから
魔女狩りや宗教裁判…
Since England is a country of magic,
witch hunts and inquisitions,
そういう対魔術師用の文化が
異常に発達したの
this kind of anti-magician culture
developed in extraordinary manners.
だから イギリス清教には
特別な部署があるんだよ
That is why the English Purist Church has a special division.
In order to defeat magicians, this division has researched magic and devised strategies against them.
魔術師を討つために
魔術を調べ上げて 対抗策を練る
It is called the church of necessary evil, "Necessarius".
必要悪の教会… ネセサリウス
（上条）ネセサリウス？
Necessarius?
But, in order to understand an impure enemy, our own hearts will become impure.
だけど
汚(けが)れた敵を理解すれば 心が汚れ
汚れた敵に触れれば 体が汚れる
Coming in contact with an impure enemy, our body will become impure.
その汚れを一手に引き受ける部署
その最たるものが…
It is a division that gathers all the impurities in one spot.
And the greatest impurity of all is-
10万3,000冊
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）うん
Those 103,000 grimoires...
Yes.
魔術っていうのは
式みたいなものだから
Magic is like a formula.
上手に逆算すれば 相手の攻撃を
中和させることもできるの
If one can successfully reverse engineer it,
one can even neutralize an adversary's attack.
世界中の魔術を知れば―
If one knows all the magic in the world,
世界中の魔術を
中和できるはずだから
one will be able to neutralize all the magic in the world.
So the 103,000 grimoires were-
私には10万3,000冊の魔道書が…
たたき込まれた
-hammered into your brain.
フン… そんなヤバイ物(もん)なら
If these were really that dangerous,
読まずに
燃やしちまえばいいじゃねえか
they should've just burned 'em and not bothered reading 'em.
重要なのは
本じゃなくて中身だから
What's important isn't the book itself but the content.
原典を消しても それを
伝え聞かせちゃったら意味がないの
Even if the original is destroyed,
it would be meaningless if it were passed down through oral tradition.
それに 原典の処分は人間にはムリ
（上条）えっ？
Besides, humans are unable to destroy the originals.
正確には 人の精神ではムリなの
The human mind is unable to, to be exact.
どうしようもないからこそ
封印するしか道がなかったんだよ
They had no choice but to seal them off because they couldn't do anything.
In other words, people are after the bomb implanted inside your head, right?
つまり 連中は
お前の頭の中にある爆弾を―
手に入れたいってわけなんだな？
10万3,000冊は―
With these 103,000 grimoires, one can absolutely be able to distort the entire world.
全て使えば 世界を
例外なく ねじ曲げることができる
てめえ… そんな大事な話
なんで今まで黙ってやがった？
You...
Why did you keep all this to yourself this whole time?!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
だって
信じてくれると思わなかったし
I didn't think you'd believe me...
怖がらせたくなかったし
それに あの…
And I didn't want to scare you...
And... I...
嫌われたくなかったから
I didn't want you to hate me...
ざけんなよ てめえ！
ナメたこと言いやがって！
Whatever, man!
You're dissing me right there!
Church of necessary evil, Necessarius?
必要悪の教会？　ネセサリウス？
10万3,000冊の魔道書？
103,000 grimoires?
とんでもねえ話だったし
聞いた今でも信じられねえ
It really does sound like bullshit,
and hearing all this would be really hard for someone to believe.
But, you know?
だけどな…
たった それだけなんだろう？
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）え…？
That's all there is to it, right?
ンッ… 見くびってんじゃねえ
Don't underestimate me.
たかが 10万3,000冊を覚えた程度で
Just because you memorized 103,000 books,
気持ち悪いとか言うと
思ってんのか？
do you think I'd consider you disgusting?
Have some faith in me!
ちったぁ 俺を信用しやがれ
人を勝手に値踏みしてんじゃねえぞ
Don't be judging people on your own, okay?
ほら！　俺ってば 右手があるから
魔術師なんざ 敵じゃねえし
See? I've got my right hand.
Magicians are no match for me.
けど 補習で学校に
行かなきゃならないって言ったから
But, you said you needed to go to school for extra lessons.
言ったっけ？
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）絶対 言った
Did I?
You definitely did.
いいんだよ 学校なんて
F-Forget school!
じゃ なんだって “学校に
行かなきゃ”とか言ってたの？
So why did you say you had to go to school?
That you had plans.
“予定があるから”って
My presence made you feel uncomfortable, huh?
私がいると 居心地悪かったんだ？
Uncomfortable, huh?
悪かったんだ？
（神裂(かんざき)）インデックスは？
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）生きてるよ
How's Index?
She's alive.
I've researched the background of the teenager accompanying her.
（神裂）
彼女に同伴していた少年の身元を
探りました
So, what's up with his right hand?
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
…で あれの右手は何だった？
（神裂）
少なくとも―
To say the least, he is not a magician or even a supernatural power user.
魔術師や異能者といった
たぐいではない …としか
Now what?
何だ？　もしかして あれが
ただの高校生とでもいうつもりかい
Are you going to tell me he's just a normal high-schooler?
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
やめてくれよ
Give me a break.
何の力も持たない素人が
イノケンティウスを退けられるほど
This world wasn't created easy enough for some amateur with no powers to be able to dispatch Innocentius.
世界は優しく作られちゃいない
（神裂）
そうですね
That is true.
Rather, the problem is his battle abilities actually belong in the category of "worthless students that like to pick fights".
むしろ 問題なのは 彼が―
ただのケンカっ早いダメ学生という
カテゴリーになっていることです
Perhaps there is an intentional blackout on his information?
情報の意図的な封鎖 …かな
しかも インデックスの傷は
魔術で癒やしたと来た
And Index's wounds were actually healed through magic.
神裂　この極東には
ほかに魔術組織が実在するのかい？
Kanzaki, do other magic societies exist in this Far East?
If they were moving inside this Academy City,
学園都市で動くとなれば―
何人(なんぴと)も理事会のアンテナに
かかるはずですが
some should at least be detected by the institution's antennae.
敵戦力は未知数
対して こちらの増援はなし
Enemy forces are unknown.
We have no backup.
She seems really happy.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
楽しそうだよね
She really does.
本当に楽しそうだ
She's been leading a happy life.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
あの子は
いつでも楽しそうに生きている
How much longer do we have to keep tearing and ripping that up?
僕たちは 一体 いつまで
あれを引き裂き続ければいいのかな
Is it a perplexing emotion for you?
（神裂）
複雑な気持ちですか？
かつて
あの場所にいた あなたとしては
You, who have been in that place in the past.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
フフッ… いつものことだよ
It's the same as always.
（上条）
結局
スーパーから帰ってきた小萌先生は
In the end, when Komoe-sensei came back from the supermarket,
何の事情も聞かずに
俺たちをアパートに泊めてくれた
she didn't ask anything and let us stay in her apartment.
Maybe she forgot all of it while she was doing her shopping,
買い物に夢中で忘れたのか
or maybe she decided to forget everything.
全部 忘れていたことに
してくれたのか
それは聞いていない
At least, I didn't ask her that.
Bath-tub! Bath-tub!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
♪ お風呂 お風呂 お風呂
Bath-tub~
Bath-tub! Bath-tub!
当麻(とうま) 当麻 当麻
（上条）うん？
Touma! Touma! Touma!
Nothing!
何でもない
用がないのに名前が呼べるって
なんか面白いかも
It's kind of fun to call someone's name without any purpose.
Right, Touma?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
ねえ 当麻
聞きたいことがあるんだよ
（上条）うん？
I want to ask you something.
小萌が言ってた…
Komoe mentioned that...
ジャパニーズ銭湯には
コーヒー牛乳という物があって
In a Japanese public bath,
there's this thing called coffee milk.
Like this,
こう！　こう！
and this,
put your hand on your hip and drink it like this!
腰に手を当てて飲むのですよ
What's this coffee milk?
コーヒー牛乳って なに？
カプチーノみたいな物？
Is it like cappuccino?
…んなエレガントな物
銭湯にはねえ
There's nothing elegant like that in a public bath.
けど お前には
でかい風呂は衝撃的かもな
You may experience a culture shock when you see the large bath, though.
イギリスって
狭っ苦しいユニットバスが―
They've got nothing but narrow bathtubs in England, right?
メジャーなんだろう？
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）う～ん…
その辺は よく分かんないかも
（上条）どうして？
I actually don't know.
Why not?
私 気がついたら 日本にいたからね
Because, I was in Japan before I realized it.
I'm not really sure about anything in England.
向こうのことは
ちょっと分からないんだよ
うん？　どうりで
日本語ペラペラのはずだぜ
No wonder you speak Japanese so fluently.
No, that's not what I meant.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
ううん
そういう意味じゃないんだよ
I was born in London and apparently was brought up inside St. George's Church.
私 生まれはロンドンで
聖(セント)ジョージ大聖堂の中で
育ってきたらしいんだよ
どうも こっちに来たのは
１年くらい前かららしいんだね
I came here about a year ago, I think.
“らしい”？
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）うん
You think?
Yeah, because my memories keep disappearing.
記憶がなくなっちゃってるからね
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
最初に目を覚ましたときは
自分のことも分からなかった
When I first awakened, I didn't even know who I was.
昨日の晩ご飯も思い出せないのに
I couldn't even recall what I ate the night before,
but I knew about magicians, Index, Necessarius...
魔術師とか インデックスとか
必要悪の教会(ネセサリウス)とか
そんな知識ばかり グルグル回って
本当に怖かった
...knowledge like that kept popping up...
I was really scared...
じゃ どうして
記憶をなくしちまったかも―
So, you don't even know why you're losing your memories?
分かんねえってことか？
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）うん
Yup!
当麻 なんか怒ってる？
Touma?
Are you angry or something?
Am not.
怒ってねえよ
何か気に障ったなら 謝るかも
I might apologize if I offended you,
当麻 なにキレてるの？
思春期ちゃん？
but what is angering you, Touma?
Going through puberty?
その幼児体型にだけは 思春期とか
聞かれたくねえよな ホント
I don't want to hear "puberty" from someone with a pedo body like you.
ムッ… 何なのかな？　それ
Gosh, what's that supposed to mean?
You are angry from what I can tell.
やっぱり怒ってるように見えるけど
それとも あれなの？
Or is it that?
当麻は 怒ってるフリして
私を困らせてる？
That you're pretending to be angry to tease me?
当麻の そういう所は嫌いかも
（上条）あのな…
I think I don't like that aspect of you, Touma.
Ok, hold it.
元から好きでもねえくせに
そんなセリフ吐くなよな
You don't even like me to begin with,
so don't be saying stuff like that.
いくら何でも お前に そこまで―
No matter how desperate I am, I don't anticipate such romantic events filled with love comments from you.
ラブコメっぽい
ステキイベントなんぞ―
期待しちゃいねえからさ …て
...huh?
あれ？　なんで上目遣いで
黙ってしまわれるのですか 姫？
Why are you being quiet and staring angrily at me like that?
My princess?
Touma!
当麻！
（上条）うん？
大っ嫌い！
I hate you!
Geez...
…たく
かむだけ かんだら １人で
さっさと行っちまいやがって
Biting me all she wants
and going on her own way like that...
あっ… あれ？
Huh?
人がいない？
There's... no one?
（神裂）ルーン
（上条）ハッ…
It's just a rune.
人払いのルーンを
刻んでいるだけですよ
A rune that removed all people from here.
てめえは…
You're...
Kanzaki Kaori is my name.
神裂火織(かおり)と申します
～♪
Next Episode
The other magician, Kanzaki Kaori.
（上条）
神裂火織と名乗る
もうひとりの魔術師
She's the one that slashed Index?
こいつがインデックスを斬った？
How can she do things like this with indifference?
なんで
こんなこと 平気でできるんだ？
Next time, "Perfect Memorization".
When science and magic cross paths,
次回 「完全記憶能力」
this epic will begin!
科学と魔術が交差するとき
物語は始まる